Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Standing committees, 1965-1986; MS2009 Series 13; 16.5 Linear feet
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 December, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Order 110 Findings of Fact, 1974 December (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Findings and Minutes December, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Pre-hearing Statement Application to Amend Zoning Map, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Brief for Respondent, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Government of the District of Columbia, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Potomac and Pennsylvania Ave. Metro Impact Area, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Reply Brief for Petitioners, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 Review of Order 110, 1974-1976 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11, undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Petitioner's memorandum in opposition, 1975 January (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Petitioner's Motion for Summary Reversal, 1975 February (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Opposition of Respondent Zoning Commission to Petitioner's Motion for Summary Reversal, 1975 March (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Petition for Review of an Order of the Zoning Commission of the District of Columbia Brief for Petitioners, 1975 May (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Petition for Review of an Order of the Zoning Commission of the District of Columbia Brief for Intervenor, 1975 June (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Petition for Review of Order of the Zoning Commission of the District of Columbia, 1977 November (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 74-11 No. 9130 Further Response by CHRS to Petition for Rehearing En Banc, 1978 June (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Cases 75-6 and 75-15 and 75-16, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 76-5, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 76-18, 1976-1978 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1969-1973 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1974-1976 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1977 March-June (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1977 July (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1977 August-September (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1977 October-December (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1978 January-March (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1978 April-July (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-2, 1979 January (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-3, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-3, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-24, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42 HERREMA DCCA and BZA, 1966-1969 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42 HERREMA Text Amendment, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42 HERREMA DCCA and BZA, 1977-1978 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42 HERREMA Text Amendment, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-42, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 77-44 Rules of Practice and Procedure, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-1 Newspaper Articles, 1977-1978 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-1 Comments and Proposals, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-1 Commercial Zone Revision, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-1 Testimony and Statements, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-1 Emergency Order, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-3, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-7P, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-12 Residential Treatment Facilities, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-12 Residential Treatment Facilities, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-12 Residential Treatment Facilities, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-12 Residential Treatment Facilities, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-12, Exhibit 143, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-13 Car Barn, 1978 May-June (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-13 Car Barn, 1978 July (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-13 Car Barn, 1978-1981 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-18 Application to Amend Zoning Map, 1979 January (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-23 Square 733, 1978 October-December (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 78-81 and 78-82 Zones Revisions, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 79-1 Treatment of Hotels order 314, 1980 May (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 79-2, 1974 January-May (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 79-20 Friends Committee, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 79-22 412 First St. S.E. PUD, undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 79-386 D.C. Court of Appeals, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 81-7 Non-conforming Use Case (1), 1982 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 81-7 Non-conforming Use Case (2), 1982 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 81-20 and 82-2, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 82-12, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 83-6, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 83-14, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 83-14 Hearings and Amendments, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 86-8 to 87, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Case 88-8C 2D and H Streets N.E., 1988 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Architect of the Capitol re: C.I.D., 1984 May (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Architect's perspective, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Articles Washington D.C. daily newspapers, 1971-1973 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Articles, other publications, 1971-1973 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Articles, undated (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Capitol East Coalition for Housing, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Capitol Hill Associates, 1970-1971 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Capitol Hill Club (First and C Streets, S.E.), 1861-1971 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Capitol Hill Defense Fund, undated (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Capitol Hill Hospital Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Capitol Hill Restoration Society, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Carbery School, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Carbon Monoxide Study, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Coalition for Neighborhood Stabilization, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Community Meeting march 11 1989 Symposium, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: D.C. Law 2-35 Community Residence Facilities Licensure Act of, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Community Relations Committee law revision committee, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Compliance, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Lewis report of 1956, Comprehensive Plan, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan Act of 1983 Bill 55-282, 1983-1984 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan Criticisms, 1983-1984 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan CHRS Statements and Testimony, 1983-1984 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan (1), 1983 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan (2), 1983 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan (3), 1983 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan (1), 1984 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Comprehensive Plan (2), 1984 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Contract, Inc., 1977 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Convention Center (1), 1977 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Convention Center (2), 1977 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Census Tracts and Data, 1940-1980 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Court of Appeals no. 5884-8827, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Court of Appeals no. 5929, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Court of Appeals no. 9130, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Court of Appeals no. 9130, undated (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Court of Appeals no. 13111 CHRS vs. BZA, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Court of Appeals no. 13321-13497, undated (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Proposed Generalized Land Use Map, 1983-2000 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia Proposed Generalized Land Use Map September, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: District of Columbia U.S. District Court Civil Actions, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: 318 East Capitol (1), 1966-1977 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: 318 East Capitol (2), undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Eastern Market Lease, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Eastern Market, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Florida House, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Georgetown Waterfront Case, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: High-rise Briefs no. 9130 (1), undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: High-rise Briefs no.9130 (2), undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: High-rise Briefs no.9130 (3), undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Historic District, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Historic District Legislation, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Home Rule and Zoning, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Land Use, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Large Tract Development, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Library of Congress James Madison Building, 1963-1971 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Metro Stations, 1971-1974 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Claudia Moore and BZA (1), undated (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Claudia Moore and BZA (2), undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Claudia Moore and BZA (3), undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Claudia Moore and BZA (4), undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: National Capital Planning Commission Zoning Committee Meeting pgs. 1-53, 1974 November 20 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: National Capital Planning Commission Zoning Committee Meeting pgs. 54-180, 1974 November 20 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: National Capital Planning Commission Zoning Committee Meeting pgs. 181-217, 1974 November 20 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: National Capital Planning Commission, undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: National Capital Planning Commission, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: National Capital Planning Commission for Element of Comprehensive Plan, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Neighbors, undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: New Jersey Avenue, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Newsletter The Commentator, ANC Winter, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Newsletter News CHRS March-June, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Newsletters, bulletins, 1969-1972 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Oklahoma House, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Pennsylvania Avenue Plan, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Planned Unit Development, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Potomac and Pennsylvania Avenues S.E., undated (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Potomac Avenue Metro Impact Area, undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Rezoning, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Rock Concert, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Rogers Memorial Hospital, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Roy Rogers, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Sam's Grocery PBC Class B License, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Carol Santos File (1), undated (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Carol Santos File (2), undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Special Exceptions/ Non-profit Use of Residential Buildings, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: South Capitol Street Buzzards Point, undated (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: South Federal Center, 1983-1985 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Square 757 purchased by architect of the Capitol, 1971-1973 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Square 757 Correspondence, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Square 757 Hearing, Congressional Record, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Testimony before other District of Columbia Board, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Transportation Cars and Rapid Transit, undated (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Union Station Bus Terminal, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: United States Congress Laws and Report, 1973-1984 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: United States Supreme Court Historical Society, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Urban Development Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Urban Development Corporation, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Urban Development Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Ward 6 Planning, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Washington D.C. Board of Elections, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Washington D.C. Map, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Washington D.C. publications, undated (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA), 1972-1974 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: West End, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Wisconsin Avenue Corridor Committee, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning Forum, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning Commission Act, 1938 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning Commission orders, 1969-1974 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning Commission, 1972-1974 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning Planning, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning Rules Revision, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning general file, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning general file, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Zoning general file, undated (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Zoning and Planning Committee: Members List, 1979; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: General Correspondence, 1974-1976; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: General Correspondence, 1975-1987; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Zoning and Planning Committee General: Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1977; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Zoning and Planning Committee General: Various Publications, 1971-1977; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 5 (1/2))
  - Zoning and Planning Committee General: Various Publications, 1971-1977; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 6 (2/2))
  - Zoning Committee: Board Meeting Notes and Notices, 1978; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Newsletters, 1975-1979; Series 13 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Correspondence and Planning, 1974-1975; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee General: News Releases and Various, 1975-1976; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee General: Correspondence, 1976-1977; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee General: Commission and Board of Adjustment Documents, 1977 - 1978; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee General: Notes and Correspondence, 1978-1979; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee General: Correspondence, 1983-1984; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee General: Correspondence and Committee Members, 1973-1974; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee General: Correspondence, 1971-1972; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee General: Newspaper Articles, 1972-1973; Series 13 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 6408-10450, 1961-1970; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 10461-11074, 1970-1974; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11143-11467, 1972-1973; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11485-11494, 1973; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11504-11510, 1973; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11515-11551, 1973 - 1974; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11555-11649, 1974; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11652-11753, 1974; Series 13 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11773-11865, 1973 - 1974; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11867-11937, 1975; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11966-11972, 1975; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 11973-11993, 1975; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12006-12027, 1975; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12030-12061, 1975 - 1976; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12074-12119, 1976; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12125-12167, 1976; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12175-12235, 1976; Series 13 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12250-12271, 1976-1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12277-12294, 1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12296-12311, 1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12312-12339, 1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12356-12383, 1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12393, Newspaper Clippings, Handwritten Notes and Official Documents, 1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12417-12499, 1977; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12505-12561, 1977-1979; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12562-12584, 1978; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12595-12618, 1978; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12645-12651, 1978; Series 13 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12659, 1977-1978; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12661-12687, 1978; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12725-12841, 1978-1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12842-12873, 1978-1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12889-12914, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12932-12935, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12951- Morgan's Property, 604 Independence Ave SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12957- Smalls Property, 1318 North Carolina Ave NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12960-12979, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12979- Gallo Property, 125 7th St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12985- Quillian Property, 820 D St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 12992- Cohen Property, 232 and 234 6th St SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13006- J.C. Associates Property, 1101 East Capitol St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13024- Gravel Property, 117 2nd St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13026- Moore Property, 122 6th St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13027- Emerson Property, 521 9th St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13032-13035, 1979; Series 13 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13039- Tripodi Property, 732 5th St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13042- Evans Property, 443 4th St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13049- Stewart Property, 1129 C St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13052- Peterson Property, 320 10th St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13053- Canal and Ivy Associates Property, 55 Ivy St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13060- Johnson Property, 629 G St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13074- Sloane Property, 331 5th St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13076- Lange Property, 306 Independence Ave SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13082- Wills Property, 314 1/2 G St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13103- Kucera Property, 121 4th St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 1312- Liberty Lobby Property, 629 Constitution Ave NW, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13135- 301 G St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13143- Hammond Jr. and Wall Property, 111 10th St. SE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13144- Elliot Street Association Property, 614 Elliot St. NE, 1979 - 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13154- Liberty Lobby Property, 629 Constitution Ave NW, 1979 - 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13158- Moore Property, 122 6th St. NE, 1979; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13162- Callahan Property, 1418 C St. NE, 1979-1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13171- David-James Builders Inc. Property, 1378 K St. SE, 1979 - 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13173- Joe Property, 720 A St. SE, 1979-1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13182- Capitol Hill Hospital Property, 822 Constitution Ave NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13188- 1401 E St. SE, 1980 March 11; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13194- 300 F St. NE, 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - Zoning Committee: Number 13197- Metropolitan Baptist Church Property, 506 East Capitol St. NE, 1979 - 1980; Series 13 (Box 152, Folder 23)